http://www.nakedart.com/about1/privacy-policy

About
Who Am I?
Returns
Nakedart frames
Privacy PolicyWhy do we need any data?We will only use your data to improve your experience.SecureWe'll protect your data like it's our own.We will send you no spamYou decide what and how you hear from us.We keep no more than we needYour info won't just hang about – if we don't need it, we'll delete it.Protecting your privacyAt Nakedart, we are 100% committed to protecting the privacy and security of our customers and site visitors. If you have any questions about how we protect your privacy, drop us a line at perry@nakedart.comHow we use your information
How we use your name & contact detailsDeliver your purchases to you - We've got to do this to perform our contract with youSend
you service messages by e-mail such as order updates - We've got to do
this to perform our contract with you, so you can tell when your order
is comingSending you information by email or post, about our new
products and services - To keep you up to date. We only send this with
your permissionFraud prevention and detection - To prevent and
detect fraud against either you or Nakedart – unfortunate, but
absolutely essentialHow we use your payment informationTake payment, and give refunds - We've got to do this to perform our contract with youFraud
prevention and detection - To prevent and detect fraud against either
you or Nakedart – unfortunate, but absolutely essentialHow we use your contact historyProvide
customer service and support - We've got to do this to perform our
contract with you, after all, you expect the best service from usTrain our staff - So that, when you contact us, you get the best possible customer serviceHow we use your purchase history and saved itemsSell
you things - We've got to do this to perform our contract with you — if
you can't put stuff into a basket, you can't buy it!Provide customer service and support, and handle returns - We've got to do this to perform our contract with youFinding out what you, and other customers, likeImprove
our website and set default options for you (such as language and
currency) - To give you the best possible shopping experienceProtect
our website - To prevent and detect fraud against either you or
Nakedart – unfortunate, but absolutely essential — and to meet our legal
obligations about looking after your dataHow we use information from accounts you link to usTo
enable you to log into our website simply and easily without having to
create a specific account - To make it easier for you to use Nakedart.com
and purchase those items you want!To provide product recommendations - So you can quickly spot things which take your fancyYou
don't have to give us any of this personal information but if you
don't, you may not be able to buy from the site, and you are unlikely to
receive our optimal overall customer experience.
But that is your
choice – and we respect that.We also anonymise and aggregate
personal information (so that it does not identify you) and use it for
purposes including testing our IT systems, research, data analysis,
improving our site and app, and developing new products and services. We
also share this information with third parties.Sharing your informationWe
do not, and will not, sell any of your personal data to any third party
– including your name, address, email address or credit card
information. We want to earn and maintain your trust, and we believe
this is absolutely essential in order do that.However, we share your
data with the following categories of companies as an essential part of
being able to provide our services to you, as set out in this
statement:Companies that do things to get your purchases to you,
such as payment service providers, warehouses, order packers, and
delivery companiesProfessional service providers, such as website hosts, who help us run our businessCredit reference agencies, law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies, so we can help tackle fraudCompanies approved by you, such as social media sitesMarketing messagesIf
you have said we can, we'll send you marketing messages by email, text,
to keep you aware of what we're up to and to help you see and find our
products. You can stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time.
You can do this:Through your account settingsBy clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in any emailBy contacting our Customer Care team Once
you do this, we will update your profile to ensure that you don't
receive further marketing messages. Please note that, as Nakedart
comprises a complex web of many inter-connecting services, it might take
a few days for all our systems to be updated, so you might get messages
from us while we process your request. Stopping marketing messages will
not stop service communications (such as order updates or where you
have expressed an interest in an activity at Nakedart, for example new
artworks). Keeping your informationWe'll
hold on to your information for as long as you have your account, or as
long as is needed to be able to provide the services to you.If reasonably necessary or required to meet legal
or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse,
or enforce our terms and conditions, we may also keep hold of some of
your information as required, even after you have closed your account or
it is no longer needed to provide the services to you.Your rightsYou have a lot of rights relating to your personal information:The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used.The right to access the personal information we hold about youThe right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about youThe right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstancesThe
right to stop direct marketing messages, which you can do through My
Account, and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at
any timeThe right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service providerIf you want to exercise your rights, have a complaint, or just have questions, please contact us : perry@nakedart.comChanges to how we Protect Your PrivacyWe
may change this page from time to time, to reflect how we are
processing your data. If we make significant changes, we will make that
clear on the Nakedart website, or by some other means of contact such as
email, so that you are able to review the changes before you continue
to use Nakedart.CookiesCookies are files stored on your
computer or device when you browse the Internet. Cookies are accessible
and detected by the website you browse, and by the companies that post
their advertisements on such websites, so that they can recognise the
browser you use. By browsing the website, you allow the storing and the
use of the cookies issued by our Website. You may accept or refuse the
storing of cookies on your computer under the conditions described at
ArticleHow to contact usWe always want to hear from our customers (especially if you feel we've let you down or could do better)Have any questions or feedback about this noticeWould like us to stop using your informationWant to exercise any of your rights as set out above, or have a complaintPlease
don't hesitate to contact us, we will be happy to
answer any questions you may have.
You can contact our privacy team by
dropping us a line at perry@nakedart.com or via the Nakedart
website. Or if you'd like to, you can write to us at:Peregrine Roskilly 14 - 15 Jackson's Way, Fowlmere, SG8 7TN
